there's a brokerage note as well which
jeffries has written on icici lombard
let's go across to abhishek for more
details on that
well i know jeffries has written on icsr
lombard they have a buy recommendation
with a target price of 1620 per share
they say that the risk reward is
improving with pickup and growth
especially on the top line for the
company so 19 correction has been seen
on the stock in last 12 months which
means uh you know that the stock has
underperformed nifty uh they are saying
that icsr lombard is now outperforming
private peers in terms of premium growth
addressing a key concern that was an
overhang on its valuation uh some time
ago so they expect momentum to continue
as bank assurance and agency channels
ramp up the third party hike is the
upside risk and they say that the new
normal roe or return on equity is around
15 to 18 percent so the stake sale and
ceo or you know succession needs to be
addressed over the next 12 to 14 months
they expect a profit a cagr growth of 24
percent between fi 23 to 25 back to you
okay thanks a lot for that uh abhisheka